As always,
相変わらず、
It's really quiet.
本当 に静かというか
I'm currently not working and I'm a university student.
今、仕事はしていなくて、大学生ってことは、
That kid did it by himself.
その子の人はさ、人でやったわけだよ
I also put on some clothes.
服もつけてやったわけだよ
That's right
そ っ
mosquito.
か
That's my grandfather's personality.
お じさんの性格なんだね
Just say whatever you like
ちょっと好きなようにさ、喋って
Let's see.
み よう
It's been a while.
久しぶりでーす
久しぶりです
How many days?
何日くらいかな?
Probably about 2 months.
2ヶ月くらいかな
It's really quiet.
本当に静かというか
I'm currently not working and I'm a university student.
今、仕事はしていなくて、大学生ってことは、
Photography work is already limited to me.
撮影の仕事とか、もう僕のところだけだよね
that's right.
そうです
It's just a matter of money, but I like it.
お金がいるだけの話なんだけど、好きなんだよね
It's a mask, just use a sample from here onwards.
マスクってさ、 ここからこの辺だけサンプル使って、
All that's left is a sample.
あとはもう、サンプル
Well, the mask is...
まあ、マスクってあと、
I mask only the sample, but
サ ンプルだけマスクするんだけど、
I don't understand
分かん
do not have.
ない
Well then, I'd like you to show me your pretty face,
じゃあ、 ちょっと綺麗な顔を見せてもらいたいから、
Huh, you can't go in?
え、すごい入れんの?
Is it really possible to enter?
すごい入れんの?
Well then,
じゃあ、
Hey uncle,
ちょっと おじさんは、
I want girls to wear skirts.
女 の子にスカートさせてもらいたい
Oh, you don't want to see it.
あ、見たくないだろ
I'll leave this aside for a moment.
これはちょっと置いておきますね
I'll handle it.
扱っておきますよ
Were you at home just now?
今、自家だったっけ?
I'm alone.
一人です
Were you alone?
一人だった?
Really, I think I should go into the gap in the room.
ほんと、部屋の隙にいちゃおうかな
I guess so.
そうなんだろう
Did she have a boyfriend?
彼氏いたのだったかな?
He wasn't there.
いなかった
Ah, not there.
あ、いない
real?
ほんと?
yes.
はい
Why?
なんでですか?
He's not there.
いないんだ
Well, hey, I live in the hallway...
まあ、ちょっと、 廊下で住んでるところは、
It's a bit rural.
ちょっと田舎ですもんね
Let me ask you something.
一つ聞いてみようかな
When was the last time you did it?
最近、したのいつ?
Just be honest, be honest.
もう、ぶっちゃけ、ぶっちゃけ
recently?
最近?
結構最近?
But it's not that recent.
でも、そんな最近でもないです
But if you don't have a boyfriend, who will you be with?
でも、彼氏いなかったらさ、誰とするわけ?
With friends.
友達と
why?
なぜ?
What are you doing?
何をしてるの?
Recently.
最近だ
What opportunities do you have to meet people?
出会い機会なんてしてるの?
Ah, I'm doing it.
あ、してる
Haven't you?
してないか
I wonder what it is.
なんだろう
We met normally, ah, yes, because we are students.
普通にしあった、あ、そう、学生だから
Maybe it's the same student?
もしかして、同じ、そういう学生の?
Oh, my friend.
あ、てかまあ、友達
Sorry for making excuses.
ごめんね、言い訳してしまって
I was really curious about it.
どうしても、気になったもんね
Well then, that's it.
じゃあ、あれだね
Because such bad children must be punished.
そういう悪い子には、お仕置きしなきゃいけないから
Hey, uncle, today too.
ちょっと、おじさんもちょっと今日は、
Let's have some adult sex.
大人のね、セックスっていうのをしようかな
Go
ゴ
M: That's why I put it on.
ム つけてやったわけだわ
I see.
そっか
It's different.
違うもんね
Namatin?
ナマチン?
game.
ゲーム
Namachin is an old man though.
ナマチンは、おじさんだけどな
He's an old man though.
お じさんだけどな
You'll be excited by the look of these panties.
このパンテ見た目で興奮するでしょ
This panty is amazing and cute.
このパンテすごい、可愛いね
There's a little gap at the bottom.
下にちょっと、何か隙間隙間があって
Wow, you did a great job, again.
すごい、お仕事されちゃったね、また
Suddenly.
いきなりね
scared?
怖い?
I'm starting to feel a little scared.
ちょっと、怯えた感じになっちゃってる
Are you okay?
大丈夫?
Wow, it's getting damp.
すごい、なんか湿ってきたよ
How many people have experienced this pussy?
このマンコってさ、経験人数何人くらいなんだろう?
Not one handed?
片手ではない?
No, not much.
いや、少ない
few?
少ない?
How many people are throwing?
何人くらい投げてるの?
5 people?
5人?
If there were 5 people at 19, it would be a small number.
19で5人だったら少ないね
surely.
確かに
Are there any of you who have become Namatin?
そのうちでナマチンになった人っているんですか?
How many people?
何人か
I'm like that too, like a child
僕もそうでしょ、子供みたい
Na.
な
Wow, I'm dying.
すごい、 死んできてちゃってる
Can I show you something?
何か見せん?
That's what I said earlier.
さっき言ってそうって